Hello, hello, hello friends, today we have appointed
a very good bank at the lowest level,
this appointment is
performing well, so see
how many times in the middle of 2019, friends, let's talk about today
and friends,
before starting the video, I
want to tell you, subscribe my channel,
subscribe
chat, I will tell you from all the levels here
and I am making this video, I
have pressure, I start getting to see a very good Jatin, let's
start making it, first of all subscribe, the
subscribers I appointed here are ready to subscribe for ₹400,
₹500,
second subscribe 44,
this means anger indicator, our Vivek, which is a
dancer, we got to see, now here
we talk about volume, a volume of 28 lakhs has been
generated here, but if we
talk about delivery position, then through delivery, we sent at 20,
which is not much and I
feel that the exchange point of the stock will
remain plate for us to see the dance, right now
if the stock is at
9280 here  ₹400 1065 and this
is the most important point for us now let's
talk about the method of appointment in the company
or dividend and
share holding pattern if we look at the shares in Uttar Pradesh then there is
no dividend at all which
you can see
quantity percent at 0.8
while doing it with the city the number was given for 2019 then it was made 155
at one ₹10 or in that it was made by ₹2
and whispered so this is a special
dividend after that dividend event is
given every year okay friends so here
I have told you now let's go to our
chart okay friends in the chat
you can see that here I have
put the yr time daily chart and it
started here okay friends so this is the
important level I had told you earlier also since then it has
come and people will suit
so this is the most important for this first of all let's
grow the mill level see from
here after appointing the duty website I would have
put the appointment here
ICICI Prudential  Okay, so I will know, if I
search for it, I will find it, okay,
now I will see everything from here,
I will take the trend line here and
color the trend line blue, okay,
so that you must subscribe to this channel, you should be the
first, so before doing this, let
me tell you
that our first lemon is done, see,
here support was taken twice, it is here 12 times,
but after taking it here, we see
that this one and a half inch, after doing that, it has been
placed here,
so in this way you will
find the support level, and yes, it is done, we have
hit the support level, okay, now let
us talk about the placement above it, which was
made, for this we will see, which level will it grow, let us
make that the second level for us and after that, the most important double, which is how many times the share has taken support and resistance here, we will make a small essay, okay, you
can see here, it was made,
after that we will make a small label above, okay, so this
middle one, which you can do,
see this, this is ours here,
now let's talk about it, the next
important one is
which  That most of the shares are closing
there, okay, so look at this, this is
our most important level and loading,
see how much rain we have taken here, okay, right
here the share repeatedly moves up in reverse,
for this the first thing is
that this level is done, after that the essay above,
this is
one of the loot,
loot was done,
how do I create it, so in this way
you will create the level and you will also do a good
butter, okay,
it has been created in both the countries, you
can calculate it in this time zone, it has been
looted,
you will not have any problem, I think
you will understand it very well, if you
create loot in the entire district, you will see
how many times the share is doing well here,
okay, now I am going to create a level here,
okay, which is going to be useful for you, okay,
see here, the number of temple
runs that were created, you can create it from the chart, so
let's do this here, I am going to create a double for you,
this is what I am going to create from here,
okay, okay, in this way I have created a double,
you  I am going to create a level here,
okay friends, if
you want to move it down a little bit, you
can also add a lancet to it, okay, so the
high that you see on this level,
you will comment it here, then
Rajesh will be tension free,
after that this
longest jam of liberty will be formed, okay because it is
working here also, okay,
in the middle of this you create a support resistance zone,
as if the share is going to be created in the middle of it, then
this registration is done,
after that both will be created here,
now I have
created a sorry to make PM, okay, now if you
want to create it in the middle of the share, you can do it
because it will be visible doing this here also, okay, so
we have created all these ribbons,
okay, now let us talk about those
labels of ours which are said for us in the coming time, so
if anyone has created his long
position, okay, then in that,
these two levels which are visible for you, they are a
little loose, okay, these will be the most important for you,
spread 468  40 Carnival
will be your second target, your target will be 458,
after that the third target or 473, after that the
level will be ₹500, ₹500 and the front or
₹100, then do it, okay, so I have told these four levels for
long-term investors, now let's
talk about the downside, the
stock is trading here right now, so
this will work as support today, make the
best
swing,
56001, I don't agree
and make 41 in 1 minute, it will be able to, then
in the essay party, the pimples back is very
important for us, that is, if you want, you
can also make this level, okay, then the
more levels you make, the more important it will be for you,
now we will only
see the chart panel, you will
not touch the levels at all, okay, because the
more levels you touch, the time mode will be on,
okay, now let's talk about the monthly chart,
okay, my purpose of making this video is to show
about our trading in the stock here,
to see the result in the tele chart, okay  Now I will
save the shares here as I have
created a weekly monthly chart, we have to say
our monthly chart, in which player all the
people will see them as bloody,
so make this our base metal,
after the app, make it above its glass,
after this on this channel it is above it and from now on
this high is trying to call back,
this neck share is in the positive direction, right now
a friend, let's
talk about the last one, come a little quickly but
you will understand it completely,
see here whether our weekly chart is
giving the same direction or not,
then after being formed, every time it has been
closing higher and
after passing near the high, it again goes down,
so the share can be at this mantra speed
that when a new phase comes, it will also make its
hike great because its high is
closed, its closing happened here
and this time it will definitely wait, okay, so all the
levels that I have created are
MLA important, I have
grown all the levels here  Okay, whoever wants to get the
level towed, here also wants to do level 2,
so let me tell you one more level
that Britain and the week is going to be visible, okay, you
can see here, people, right here,
our support in the week is
white, so that's why there are important levels, I wo
n't tell you again and again, I have
explained it to you very well in every video, now let's
talk about the daily chart, okay, so the
daily chart will make everything clear to us as to
how things are going, see here the
daily chart is made, in that we
will discuss that what you can see in the description of the stock
right now is within two days
and after the formation of this candle,
you all know that the price comes daily in the share, that is, the
price increases or decreases, now
if we talk about the train, then
in April, this oil had
formed a low here, after that it formed a high here,
after that it formed a low, then it
formed a low, then it formed a high, and it has
support here twice, to see this flame,
okay, but now I feel this
hair  If tomorrow this project
is done among the people of this channel then this bell will target your number,
it is okay, whoever
wants to make a loan, wants to install it in this,
which makes people
pregnant,
tell it to open below it, first you have to wait, if it
reaches the kilo, it opens somewhere, but
people see, then you have to send it and
keep the lo of pet artist small ghee,
which is very, if both the apps are open
because if it is open then first you have to wait
till the back portion is made, then
you have to do it and you should
subscribe to this channel friends, the second channel for ₹10,
this is the most important
life, this will be your third oil level,
now let's talk about those positions, I am
not seeing the bank position anywhere in it since yesterday, it may be
down for a day or two, after that it is setting again,
okay, so this is what I am going to tell you because tomorrow
one day the share in it will work here and
after that, see this here,
take support here, take
support here and it may happen, let's go  Support here,
after that there is
no question at all in this and if someone
wishes to make it then I will
tell you that
you should hold your position as long as you want and wait,
something has been deleted
and after that share it and you all
know which one it is, if you
want it then I will tell you that it is of
APK, you can see that it is like this, it is
working very well for us and the share is currently running below it,
okay if you want to join some more people then
you will understand it well, okay so the share is also
running near it, if you
want the extract then I will make it and tell you, I am
seeing the way it is working, the
people of this game have to
join this channel, if you
want then this channel is worth it and if we join it then a
very long train
line will be formed, but right now we are going to make a black school van,
okay it is like this, I will change the color
so that our black
color can be seen well  And I will evict it, okay,
it happened like this and if someone
wants to keep a target, then I have already told the target
and I have already told your level in it,
so the first target
for those who want to keep it in the long term will be
between 472 to north, for others around ₹500
and the sharp ₹500, I think that the
coming moment in the city will be very good
and we will create this channel for you,
it is trending like this, okay,
so it will work in the coming time, in this
way you can also make your own trend line, there
is no need for MS
because the shares have just fallen, it is
not working, okay, it is working within the level, so if you
make it in the coming time, then it
and its people will do it, it will be useful for you,
okay, the
way it will be most important for us, it will
also be useful in the
coming time, now let's talk about the movie
Navratri, the Englishman has also given his approval here,
Friday has given legal increase
and  Right now, if this level call
breaks, then you have made your bike
question, but I am
seeing celebration here and if
even a slight fall in the stock
remains in the soil, then the stock will
work exactly according to you, like I
told the level, okay, friends, so I think you must have
liked the video very much and DJ
Punjabi is made, you should know
what happens, okay, so here you can
see people like macro channel, what a good moment we have got
and as it operates the hi,
okay, here it inspires the hi, so
how good it is to get on top, there are
plus points of the plane and here this is our
lipid level, this is the most important double eighty
music, so I
made Audi cycle here, you must
also like to work on your own, so
very good, friends, so I have
also told all the points for you here and
I think that if we cross trading in the city, then it is
very good,
thank you to you and Urmila in this, friends, see you
in the new video, if you liked this video, then
definitely subscribe to the channel
and press the bell, thank you friends, see you